Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Policies and procedures, 1965 - 2003; F-33-3; 83 cm of textual records
  - Administrative policies (AD series), 1969 - 2003; F-33-3-8; 11 cm of textual records
    - AD 10.4 Modification of appointments from full-time to part-time, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-68 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.5 Position share, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-69 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.6 Position evaluation and salary administration, 1999 - 2000; F-33-3-8-0-70 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-209.
    - AD 10.7 Group benefit plans, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-71 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.8 Leaves with and without pay, 1999 - 2000; F-33-3-8-0-72 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-210.
    - AD 10.9 Professoinal development leave, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-73 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.10 Training and professional development, 1999 - 2000; F-33-3-8-0-74 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-211.
    - AD 10.11 APSA professional development allowance, 1999 - 2000; F-33-3-8-0-75 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-212.
    - AD 10.12 Tuition waiver, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-76 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.13 Work schedules, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-77 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.14 No discrimination, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-78 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.15 Strike policy, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-79 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.16 Performance evaluation, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-80 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.17 Problem resolution, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-81 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.18 Elimination of positions and employment continuity, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-82 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.19 Discipline and termination of employment, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-83 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.20 Resignation, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-84 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 11-1 Statement of purchasing policy and responsibility, 1971 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-85 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-117.
    - AD 11-2 Request for quotation, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-86 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-118.
    - AD 11-3 Requisitioning materials and services, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-87 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-119.
    - AD 11-5 Emergency purchases, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-88 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-120.
    - AD 11-6 Petty cash purchases, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-89 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-121.
    - AD 11-7 Standing and blanket purchase orders, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-90 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-122.
    - AD 11-8 Purchase of special equipment, 1973 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-91 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-123.
    - AD 11-9 Customs clearances, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-92 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-124.
    - AD 11-10 Reporting and disposal of surplus equipment and material, 1973 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-93 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-125.
    - AD 11-11 Expediting, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-94 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-126.
    - AD 11-12 Ordering of printing, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-95 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-127.
    - AD 11-13 Purchase or lease of land, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-96 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-128.
    - AD 11-14 Local purchase orders, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-97 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-129.
    - AD 11-15 Tenders and contracts, 1972 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-98 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-130.
    - AD 11-16 Damaged shipments, 1970 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-99 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-131.
    - AD 11-17 Central Stores storage, 1971 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-100 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-132.
    - AD 11-18 Conflict of interest, 1971 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-101 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-133.
    - AD 11-19 Cutoff dates - fiscal year end purchases, 1975 - 1993; F-33-3-8-0-102 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-134.
    - AD 11-20 Central Stores pick-up and delivery service, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-103 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-135.
    - AD 13-1 Project requests, 1974 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-104 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-136.
    - AD 13-2 Work orders (total cost under $750.00), 1975 - 1984; F-33-3-8-0-105 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-137.
    - AD 13-2 Minor capital project requests (total cost over $1500), 1994; F-33-3-8-0-106 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - AD 13-3 Minor work order requests, 1979 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-107 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-138.
    - AD 13-4 Murals and displays of art works, 1980; F-33-3-8-0-108 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-139.
    - AD 13-5 Display of notices, posters, advertisements, etc. on campus, 1984; F-33-3-8-0-109 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-140.
    - AD 14-1 Telephone service, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-110 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-141.
    - AD 14-2 Long distance telephone charges, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-111 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-142.
    - AD 14-3 Maintenance and repair of office machines, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-112 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-143.
    - AD 14-4 Central Stores requisitioning, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-113 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-144.
    - AD 14-5 Central Stores storage, 1989; F-33-3-8-0-114 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-145.
    - AD 14-6 Central Stores pick-up and delivery service, 1983 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-115 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-146.
  - General policies (G series), 1972 - 2003; F-33-3-9; 7 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of G series policies and their revisions over time.
    - GP Series policy list, 1984 - 1995; F-33-3-9-0-1 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-147.
    - GP 1 Appointment of acting administrators in cases of absence, 1972 - 1980; F-33-3-9-0-2 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-148.
    - GP 2 Political leave, 1974; F-33-3-9-0-3 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-149.
    - GP 3 Donations, 1974 - 1996; F-33-3-9-0-4 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-150.
    - GP 4 Closure of the University, 1974 - 1995; F-33-3-9-0-5 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-151.
    - GP 5 Strike policy - SFU, 1975; F-33-3-9-0-6 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-152.
    - GP 6 Name and address data (on computer), 1977; F-33-3-9-0-7 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-153.
    - GP 7 Word processing, 1979; F-33-3-9-0-8 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-154.
    - GP 8 Delegation of authority, 1980; F-33-3-9-0-9 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-155.
    - GP 9 Relocation expenses, 1980 - 2001; F-33-3-9-0-10 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-156.
    - GP 10 Special fees, 1981; F-33-3-9-0-11 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-157.
    - GP 11 Policy for Images Theatre, 1981; F-33-3-9-0-12 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-158.
    - GP 12 Employment of personnel funded from research grants and contracts, 1985 - 1986; F-33-3-9-0-13 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-159.
    - GP 13 The office computer workstation, 1985 - 1987; F-33-3-9-0-14 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-160.
    - GP 14 Visiting film companies, 1985 - 1993; F-33-3-9-0-15 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-161.
    - GP 15 Archives and records management policy, 1986; F-33-3-9-0-16 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-162.
    - GP 16 Smoking policy, 1987 - 2000; F-33-3-9-0-17 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-163.
    - GP 17 University occupational health and safety, 1988 - 1999; F-33-3-9-0-18 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-164.
    - GP 18 Human rights policy, 1987 - 2003; F-33-3-9-0-19 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-165.
    - GP 19 Employment equity policy, 1989 - 1992; F-33-3-9-0-20 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-166.
    - GP 20 Endowment management, 1991 - 1998; F-33-3-9-0-21 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-167.
    - GP 21 Disposal of broken glass and sharps, 1991; F-33-3-9-0-22 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-168.
    - GP 22 Fire procedures, 1992; F-33-3-9-0-23 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-169.
    - GP 23 University policy on international activities, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-9-0-24 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-170.
    - GP 24 Fair use of information resources, 1993; F-33-3-9-0-25 (Archival box - small 33-89)
    - GP 25 Response to violence and threatening behaviour, 1993 - 2003; F-33-3-9-0-26 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-224.
    - GP 26 Accessibility policy for students with disabilities, 1994 - 1995; F-33-3-9-0-27 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-213.
    - GP 28 University trade marks: registration and licensing for commercial uses, 1997; F-33-3-9-0-28 (Archival box - small 33-89)
    - GP 29 Search committees for vice-presidents and associate vice-presidents, 1999 - 2001; F-33-3-9-0-29 (Archival box - small 33-89)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-214.
    - GP 32 Environmenal management policy, 2003; F-33-3-9-0-30 (Archival box - small 33-89)
    - GP 33 Animal/pet policy, 2003; F-33-3-9-0-31 (Archival box - small 33-89)
  - Board of Governors policies (B series), 1992 - 2003; F-33-3-10; 2 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of B series policies and their revisions over time.
    - Board regulations, 1992; F-33-3-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-205.
    - B 10.01 Rules of the Board, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.02 Terms of reference and procedures for Board committees, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.03 Policy on Senate actions, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.04 Policy on faculty appointments, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.05 Budget policy objectives, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.06 Presidential search committee, 1995; F-33-3-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.07 Contracting of University services, 1996; F-33-3-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.08 Executive compensation, 1996; F-33-3-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - B 10.09 Investment governance, 2003; F-33-3-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
  - Information policies (I series), 1994 - 2003; F-33-3-11; 2 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of I series policies and their revisions over time.
    The files are open with no restrictions..
    - I 10.01 Archives, recorded information management, freedom of information and protection of privacy, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.02 Head of the institution and delegation of authority, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 0.03 Freedom of information fee schedule, 1994; F-33-3-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.04 Access to information and protection of privacy, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.05 Collection of personal information, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.06 Requests that create conflict of interest, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.07 Security of facsimile transmissions, 1997; F-33-3-11-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.08 Collection and disclosure of instructor and course evaluations, 1998; F-33-3-11-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.09 Retention and disposal of student exams or assignments, 1998; F-33-3-11-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - I 10.10 Confidentiality policy, 2003; F-33-3-11-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
- Correspondence, 1965 - 1977; F-33-4; 9 cm of textual records
  Series includes correspondence of Board officers including secretaries (C. J. Frederickson and R. E. Lester); and chairs (R. E. Lester, Kenneth Caple, and Paul Cote).
  - Chair's correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-33-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
  - Chair's correspondence, 1971; F-33-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
  - Chair's correspondence, 1966 - 1970; F-33-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
  - Secretary's correspondence, 1965 - 1974; F-33-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
  - Report of the Senior Management Committee, 1977; F-33-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
- Board reports, 1965 - 1968; F-33-5; 2 cm of textual records
  Series comprises 33 reports to the faculty of Simon Fraser University regarding actions taken by the Board of Governors. Also includes a progress report on the University Library.
  - Board Reports. Sept. 1965 - May 1968, 1965 - 1968; F-33-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
- Special hearings, 1969; F-33-6; 8 sound recordings; Physical description: recordings comprise 14 audio tapes (originals) and 18 audio cassettes (access copies).
  In the fall of 1969, nine professors in the Department of Political Science, Sociology, and Anthropology withdrew their services in response to the department being put under trusteeship by the University administration. The University appointed a trustee because of allegations of departmental mismanagement of finances. The department also did not produce a constitution and tenure committee structure that were acceptable to the University administration. Various student and faculty support strikes and protest actions followed. The President suspended nine PSA faculty members who were most actively involved in the strike and later fired seven of them.
  The series comprises audio recordings of the suspension hearings held by the Board of Governors for six of those faculty members. The Board conducted the hearings to enable faculty members to appeal their suspension by the President. In each case, the Board upheld the decision by the President to suspend the faculty members. Additional legal proceedings followed the suspension hearings.
  Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology
  - PSA hearings: K.G. Aberle, October 31, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-549, Audio cassette OBJ-550, Audio reel OBJ-595, Audio reel OBJ-596)
    Aberle, Kathleen; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-02, R-33-6-0-1, R-33-6-0-2, F-33-item1, F-33-item2.
  - PSA hearings: K.G. Aberle, November 17, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-592, Audio reel OBJ-597)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-02, R-33-6-0-1, R-33-6-0-2, F-33-item3.
  - PSA hearings: Saghir Ahmad, November 19, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-591, Audio cassette OBJ-536, Audio cassette OBJ-535, Audio reel OBJ-598, Audio reel OBJ-599)
    Ahmad, Saghir; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-0-4, F-33-item4, F-33-item5.
  - PSA hearings: Prudence Wheeldon, November 20, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-4 (Audio reel OBJ-600, Audio reel OBJ-601, Audio cassette OBJ-537, Audio cassette OBJ-538, Audio cassette OBJ-539)
    Wheeldon, Prudence; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-0-6, F-33-item6, F-33-item7.
  - PSA hearings: Mordecai Briemberg, November 21, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-540, Audio cassette OBJ-541, Audio reel OBJ-602, Audio reel OBJ-603)
    Briemberg, Mordecai; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-0-8, F-33-item8, F-33-item9.
  - PSA hearings: Louis Feldhammer, November 24, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-542, Audio cassette OBJ-543, Audio cassette OBJ-544, Audio cassette OBJ-545, Audio reel OBJ-604, Audio reel OBJ-605)
    Feldhammer, Louis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-0-10, F-33-item10, F-33-item11.
  - PSA hearings: John Leggett, December 2, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-546, Audio cassette OBJ-547, Audio reel OBJ-606, Audio reel OBJ-607)
    Leggett, John C.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R 33-6-0-12, R 33-6-0-13, F-33-item12, F-33-item13.
  - PSA hearings: Mordecai Briemberg, December 10, 1969; F-33-6-0-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-548, Audio reel OBJ-608)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: R-33-6-0-14, F-33-item14.
- Presidential committees, 1968 - 1979; F-33-7; 12 cm of textual records
  The Board established a Presidential Search Committee in 1968, in 1973, and again in 1978 to recommend candidates for the position of University President. The committees included Board members: faculty, administration, and student representatives; and later alumni and employee representatives. The series contains records relating to the work of these committees.
  Includes correspondence, agendas, minutes, terms of reference, procedures, lists of candidates, c.v.'s, reports, press releases, and clippings.
  - Terms of Reference, 1968 - 1973; F-33-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Committee nominations: support papers, 1968 - 1973; F-33-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 1969; F-33-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Board of Governor's minutes, 1969; F-33-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Student involvement: minutes and papers, 1968 - 1969; F-33-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - List of candidates, 1969; F-33-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Candidate short list and support papers, 1968 - 1969; F-33-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Terms of reference: support papers, 1968 - 1973; F-33-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 1973 - 1974; F-33-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
  - Search committee procedures and composition, 1975 - 1979; F-33-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-82)
- Committees, 1968-2009; F-33-8
  This series comprises records pertaining to the establishment, execution of responsibilities, integration, and dissolution of committees; as well as task forces formed to support the Board of Governors in achieving its objectives. It encompasses standing committees and ad hoc committees. The records include committee meeting agendas, minutes, and notes; memos; reports; budget projections; project plans; correspondence; contracts; bargaining agreements; proposals; curriculum vitae and applications; policies and procedures; financial statements; terms of reference; promotional materials and articles; lists of award recipients; student surveys; and presentations.
  Each committee was established as its own sub-series. The sub-series' were then arranged chronologically, in relation to the date of records creation.
  The sub-series' [Presidential Search and Review Committees](f-33-1-1) and [Executive Search and Review Committees](f-33-12) represent an aggregate of committees. They are further broken down into sub-sub-series for each individual committee.
  Further accruals are expected.
  - Presidential Search and Review Committees, 1968-2009; F-33-8-1; 73 cm of textual records
    Since 1968, the Board has been establishing Presidential Search Committees to recommend suitable candidates for appointment as President of SFU. Additionally, Committees to Review the President Prior to Reappointment have been set up to assess current Presidents for potential reappointment. Both types of committees include Board members, faculty, administration, student representatives, and later on, alumni, employee, and student representatives.
    This sub-series comprises records related to the activities of both the Presidential Search Committees and the Committees for Presidential Review Prior to Reappointment. It also includes any records associated with the annual presidential review that support the process of reappointment. The records encompass meeting agendas, minutes, and documents; agreements and contracts; terms of reference; procedures and policies; candidate lists; correspondence; curriculum vitae; applications; letters of recommendation; advertisements; memos; reports; press releases; and clippings.
    - 1968-1979 Presidential Search Committees, F-33-8-1-1; 12 cm of textual records